var questions = 
      [
        {
          "question": "If Shayan Meet with Genie what should be Shayan's wish?",
          "option1": "A Billion Of Dollors",
          "option2": "Beautiful Wife", 
          "option3": "Become most handsome man in the world", 
          "option4": "To be President/Prime Minister",
          "answer": "1"
        },
        
        {
          "question": "What Does Shayan Drink The Most?",
          "option1": "Tea",
          "option2": "Cofee", 
          "option3": "Coke", 
          "option4": "Alcohol",
          "answer": "1"
        },

        {
          "question": "Where Would Shayan Like To Go With Shayan's SoulMate?",
          "option1": "London",
          "option2": "Paris", 
          "option3": "New York", 
          "option4": "Kashmir",
          "answer": "4"
        },

        {
          "question": "Which One id Shayan's Favourite PSL team?",
          "option1": "Karachi Kings",
          "option2": "Islamabad United", 
          "option3": "Peshawar Zalmi", 
          "option4": "Quetta Gladiators",
          "answer": "2"
        },

        {
          "question": "Which Animal Does Shayan's Dream Pet?",
          "option1": "A Dog",
          "option2": "A Cat", 
          "option3": "Baby Tiger", 
          "option4": "Gold Fish",
          "answer": "3"
        },


        {
          "question": "Which One is The Shayan's Favourite Movie?",
          "option1": "Titanic",
          "option2": "The Conjuring", 
          "option3": "The Avengers", 
          "option4": "Harry Potter",
          "answer": "3"
        },


        {
          "question": "In Free Time, What Would Shayan do?",
          "option1": "Sketching",
          "option2": "Listen Songs", 
          "option3": "Programing", 
          "option4": "Watch Movie",
          "answer": "2"
        },


        {
          "question": "What Would Shayan Do If Shayan Won A lottery?",
          "option1": "Travel The World",
          "option2": "Invest It", 
          "option3": "Buy A Sport Car", 
          "option4": "Donate",
          "answer": "4"
        },

        {
          "question": "Which One Is The Shayan's Favourite Celebrity?",
          "option1": "Micheal Jackson",
          "option2": "Jonny Deep", 
          "option3": "Saleena Gomez", 
          "option4": "Robert Downey Jr.",
          "answer": "1"
        },


        {
          "question": "Which one is the Shayan's Favourite Color?",
          "option1": "Red", 
          "option2": "Yellow", 
          "option3": "Blue",
          "option4": "Light Green",
          "answer": "4"
        }


        ];